Guide to the Vassar College Student Materials Collection, 1859-2025 (bulk 1867-1950)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES XI. PHOTOGRAPH ALBUMS, 1865-circa 1989; [336 volumes]
  - VC 1874 — Reed, Annie M. (Album 18)
  - VC Ex 1874 — Stillman, Charlotte E. (Album 19)
  - VC 1875 — Barnes, Lucy (Sellers) (Album 39)
  - VC 1875 — Clark Emma [Elizabeth] (Album 12)
  - VC 1875 — Hollister, Emma B., 1872-1876 (Album 14)
  - VC 1876 — Markham, Mary (Album 74)
  - VC 1876 — Sharpe, Sara J. (Album 24)
  - VC 1877 — Gray, Lilly (Putnam), undated (Album 33)
  - VC 1877 — Phinney, Jessie (Woodward) (Album 26)
  - VC 1877 — Wood, Ida, circa 1874-1877 (Album 23)
  - VC 1878 — Hubbard, Mary T. (Album 73)
  - VC 1878 — McCaleb, Ella, 1919 (Album 229)
  - VC 1878 — Peirce, Lydia (Album 40)
  - VC 1878 — Peirce, Lydia (Ray) (Album 71)
  - VC [1878?] — Unidentified (Album 17)
  - VC 1879 — [Braden, Nannie H.?], circa 1875-1879 (Album 22)
  - VC 1879 — Dimock, Elizabeth (Jordan) (Album 8)
  - VC 1879 — Edwards, Mary Cookingham (Album 35)
  - VC 1879 — Unidentified (Album 27)
  - VC [1879?] — Unidentified [g. Mrs. C. Norman Fletcher] (Album 25)
  - VC Ex 1880 — Babbott, Lydia (Pratt) (Album 34)
  - VC 1880 — Knight, Marietta (Barnes) (Album 32)
  - VC 1880 — Knight, Marietta (Barnes) (Album 69)
  - VC 1880 — Thorsen, Caroline M. (Canfield) (Album 21)
  - VC 1880 — Unidentified (Album 20)
  - VC [1880?] — Unidentified, 1867-1880 (Album 11)
  - VC 1882 — Broadhead, Stella P. (Album 42)
  - VC 1882 — Conable, Mary (Easton) (Album 43)
  - VC 1882 — Sanford, Mary R. (Album 41)
  - VC 1882 — Wheeler, Jessie, 1878-1932 (Album 36)
  - VC 1882 — Wyman, Anne (Southworth) (Album 44)
  - VC 1883 — Hadley, Helen (Morris) (Album 48)
  - VC 1883 — Jones, Martha (Boyd), 1882-1883 (Album 46)
  - VC 1883 — Markham, Frances Garland (Album 49)
  - VC 1883 — Slee, Emeline G. (Album 50)
  - VC 1883-1884 [Special] — Hosmer, Margaret (Bagley), undated (Album 47)
  - VC 1884 — Crandall, Catharine (Patterson) (Album 54)
  - VC 1884 — Creager, Lydia (Mitchell) (Album 56)
  - VC 1884 — Harding, Elizabeth (McMillan), undated (Album 293)
  - VC 1884 — Townsend, Emily Allison (Album 51)
  - VC 1885 — Durfee, Harriet A. (Album 58)
  - VC 1885 — Fulton, Bertrice (Shattuck), undated (Album 57)
  - VC 1885 — Leonard, Ella S. (Album 70)
  - VC 1886 — Botsford, Helen C. (Album 61)
  - VC 1886 — Cooley, Nellie (Wooster) (Album 59)
  - VC 1886 — Cooley, Nellie (Wooster) (Album 60)
  - VC 1886 — Newell, Louise L. — snapshots, including many interiors (Album 90)
  - VC 1886 — Sherwood, Margaret P. (Album 62)
  - VC 1886 — Unidentified, undated (Album 82)
  - VC 1886 — Witkowsky, Esther (Album 63)
  - Members of the faculty, 1886 (Album 55)
  - VC 1888 — Briggs, Grace (Rideout) (Album 66)
  - VC 1888 — Briggs, Grace (Rideout) (Album 67)
  - VC 1888 — Briggs, Grace (Rideout) (Album 68)
  - VC Ex 1888 — Brinkerhoff, Julia, circa 1885-1889 (Album 307)
  - VC 1888 — Faust, Frances (Patterson)— tin types, undated (Album 258)
  - VC 1889 — Bond, Mabel (Cornish) (Album 64)
  - VC 1889 — Bond, Mabel (Cornish) (Album 65)
  - VC 1889 — Catterall, Helen (Tunnicliff) (Album 77)
  - VC 1889 — Catterall, Helen (Tunnicliff) (Album 78)
  - VC 1889 — Freeman, Corinne (Keen) (Album 87)
  - VC 1889 — Freeman, Corinne (Keen) (Album 88)
  - VC 1889 — Hood, Mary Katharine (Hunt) (Album 79)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson), circa 1890 (Album 147)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson), circa 1890 (Album 148)
  - VC 1890 — Rockwell, Anna G., 1887-1890 (Album 81)
  - VC 1891 — Furness, Caroline (Album 37)
  - VC 1891 — Gorham, Florence (Halliday), undated (Album 75)
  - VC 1892 — Unidentified, 1888-1892 (Album 80)
  - VC 1893 — Woodruff, Eleanor B. [housed with Album no. 125] (Album 38)
  - VC 1894 — Gilmer, Elizabeth A., circa 1892-circa 1896 (Album 339)
  - VC 1894 — Haight, Elizabeth Hazelton [housed with Album no. 125], undated (Album 52)
  - VC 1894 — Haight, Elizabeth Hazelton, undated (Album 53)
  - VC 1894 — Nollen, Emeline (Bartlett) [formerly Album no. 153, see Emeline Bartlett Nollen Scrapbook (VC 1894) ], 1866-1907
  - VC 1895 — Thorne, Elisabeth G., circa 1895 (Album 312)
  - VC 1896 — McKean, Ida P., undated (Album 83)
  - VC 1896 — Reynolds, Kate B., undated (Album 89)
  - VC 1896 — Russell, Lucile (Cross), 1895-1896 (Album 76)
  - VC Class of 1896 (Album 155)
  - VC 1897 — Beckwith, Frances A., undated (Album 99)
  - VC 1897 — Bishop, Elizabeth H. and Helen L. (Album 123)
  - VC 1897 — Burchard, Anna T., 1893-1897 (Album 189)
  - VC 1897 — Cushing, Nellie (Ferrell) [includes images of Native Americans near Fort Yates, North Dakota (Black Bull, Swift Dog) and Fort Keogh, Montana (Wooden Leg)], circa 1893-1900 (Album 94)
  - VC 1897 — Hawkins, Mary (Chambers), undated (Album 96)
  - VC 1897 — McGill, Beatrice (Shaw), circa 1893-1897 (Album 292)
  - VC 1897 — Smith, Gertrude (cyanotypes), undated (Album 95)
  - VC 1897 — Taylor, Louise Clinton (Album 158)
  - VC 1898 — Borden, Fanny (cyanotypes), 1894-1908 (Album 124)
  - VC Class of 1898 (Album 156)
  - VC 1899 — Brown, Mabel, undated (Album 93)
  - VC 1899 — Vassar College (Album 154)
  - VC 1900 — Mooney, Mabel (Schmidt), undated (Album 92)
  - VC Class of 1900 — "The Voice of the Pack," Vol. 1 (Album 117)
  - VC Class of 1900 — "The Voice of the Pack," Vol. 2 (Album 118)
  - VC Class of 1900 — "The Voice of the Pack," Vol. 3 (Album 119)
  - VC 1901 — Warner, Mary (Whitman) (Album 85)
  - VC 1901 — Warner, Mary (Whitman) (Album 86)
  - "A Souvenir of Vassar College", 1901 (Album 120)
  - VC 1902 — Mangan, Elizabeth (Everts), undated (Album 112)
  - VC 1902 — Moore, Elizabeth, 1899-1902 (Album 84)
  - VC 1902 — Utter, Grace L., circa 1898-1902 (Album 298)
  - VC 1902 — Whiteside, Mary (Myers), undated (Album 97)
  - VC 1902 — Whiteside, Mary (Myers), undated (Album 98)
  - VC Class of 1902 (Album 157)
  - VC 1903 — Anderson, Harriet [formerly Album no. 162, see Harriet Anderson Papers (VC 1903)], undated
  - VC 1903 — Gregory, Louise Hoyt, 1901 (Album 91)
  - VC 1903 — Gregory, Louise Hoyt (Album 187)
  - VC 1903 — Mahon, Josephine D., undated (Album 125)
  - VC 1903 — Spencer, Effa H., undated (Album 201)
  - VC 1904 — Best, Elenora (Ambler), undated (Album 181)
  - VC 1904 — Holmes, Mabel (Album 186)
  - VC 1904 — McKinnon, Maude, 1900-1904 (Album 288)
  - VC 1904 — Osborne, Minette (Hegeman), undated (Album 126)
  - VC 1904 — Sebring, Helen, circa 1900-1908 (Album 325)
  - VC 1904 — Taylor, Jeannette S. (Album 264)
  - VC 1904 — Thompson, A. Louise (Henry), undated (Album 204)
  - VC 1905 — Guthrie, Claire (Reiley) (Album 129)
  - VC 1905 — Guthrie, Claire (Reiley), undated (Album 205)
  - VC 1905 — Kenyon, Helen, undated (Album 114)
  - VC 1905 — Kenyon, Helen, undated (Album 115)
  - VC 1905 — Kenyon, Helen, undated (Album 116)
  - VC 1905 — Kenyon, Helen, undated (Album 281)
  - VC 1905 — Nelson, Jeannette (Ware) — includes shots of John Burroughs, circa 1904-1905 (Album 283)
  - VC 1905 — Ross, Caroline (Barnes), circa 1901-1905 (Album 306)
  - VC 1905 — Street, Emeline (Album 135)
  - VC 1906 — Fair, Ethel M., undated (Album 131)
  - VC Ex 1906 — Fuller, Alice M., undated (Album 130)
  - VC Ex 1906 — Fuller, Alice M., undated (Album 206)
  - VC 1906 — Hamilton, Mary C., circa 1902-1906 (Album 319)
  - VC 1906 — McGirr, Alice Thurston, undated (Album 137)
  - VC 1906 — Unidentified [includes 2 loose news clippings], circa 1902-1906 (Album 318)
  - VC 1906 — Unidentified [loose pages] (Album 136)
  - VC 1907 — Belknap, Mary C., undated (Album 101)
  - VC 1907 — Belknap, Mary C., undated (Album 102)
  - VC 1907 — Cutler, Ruth E., undated (Album 103)
  - VC 1907 — Cutler, Ruth E., undated (Album 104)
  - VC 1907 — Kennedy, Katherine Brown (Worcester), circa 1903-1907 (Album 322)
  - VC 1907 — Kennedy, Katherine Brown (Worcester), circa 1903-1907 (Album 323)
  - VC 1907 — Lyall, Margaret, undated (Album 100)
  - VC 1907 — Roden, Elizabeth Bowman, circa 1907 (Album 331)
  - VC 1907 — Sague, Mary (Landon), undated (Album 110)
  - VC 1907 — St. Peter, Helen Clemence, circa 1903-1910 (Album 282)
  - VC 1907 — Unidentified [housed with Album no. 125], circa 1903-1907 (Album 113)
  - VC 1908 — [Meyers, Pauline] (Album 275)
  - VC 1908 — Cox, Anna (Sellers), undated (Album 108)
  - VC 1908 — Cox, Anna (Sellers), undated (Album 109)
  - VC 1908 — Crawford, Lesley Buckland (Album 294)
  - VC 1908 — Hall, Celia (Hotchkiss), undated (Album 127)
  - VC 1908 — Hammer, Hilda, undated (Album 106)
  - VC 1908 — Oppenheimer, Edna (Sidenberg), undated (Album 111)
  - VC 1908 — Thornbury, [Zita L.] (travel album), 1920s (Album 210)
  - VC 1908 — VanCleef, Eugenia, undated (Album 107)
  - VC 1909 — Holmes, Frances (McCord) (Album 105)
  - VC 1909 — Searles, Marjorie (Squier), undated (Album 280)
  - VC 1909 — Stratton, Ethel (Hannah), circa 1906-1909 (Album 327)
  - VC 1909 — Weil, Edith, circa 1905-1909 (Album 309)
  - VC 1910 — Hawk, Della J., circa 1910 (Album 286)
  - VC 1910 — Thom, Katharine (Bissell), undated (Album 160)
  - VC 1910 — Thom, Katharine (Bissell), undated (Album 161)
  - VC 1910 — Vernlund, Alice (Farmer) (Album 274)
  - VC 1910 — Warner, Margaret L., undated (Album 128)
  - VC 1911 — Ashton, Beatrice (Owens), undated (Album 169)
  - VC 1911 — Ashton, Beatrice (Owens), undated (Album 170)
  - VC 1911 — Chapman, Virginia (Butler), undated (Album 179)
  - VC 1911 — Doane, Helen (Paine), undated (Album 171)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford), circa 1907-1911 (Album 290)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford), 1907-1908 (Album 291)
  - VC 1911 — Jones, Beulah (Tompkins), undated (Album 132)
  - VC 1911 — Jones, Beulah (Tompkins), undated (Album 133)
  - VC 1911 — Jones, Beulah (Tompkins), undated (Album 134)
  - VC 1911 — Lovejoy, Julia, circa 1907-1911 (Album 329)
  - VC 1911 — Thompson, Helen (Lathrop), undated (Album 185)
  - VC 1912 — Clary, Marjorie (Stewart), undated (Album 149)
  - VC 1912 — Clary, Marjorie (Stewart), undated (Album 150)
  - VC 1912 — Hutchinson, E. Lillian, undated (Album 183)
  - VC 1912 — James, Helen C., undated (Album 165)
  - VC 1912 — Lutz, Alma, undated (Album 164)
  - VC 1912 — Morrill, Elizabeth (Cutter), undated (Album 233)
  - VC 1912 — Morrill, Elizabeth (Cutter), undated (Album 234)
  - VC 1912 — Morrill, Elizabeth (Cutter), undated (Album 235)
  - VC 1912 — Piersol, Margaret Wessell, circa 1908-1912 (Album 320)
  - VC 1912 — Sauer, Verra L. [housed with Album no. 130], undated (Album 152)
  - VC 1913 — Dayton, Elinor (Buss), undated (Album 144)
  - VC 1913 — Dodge, Elizabeth, circa 1909-1913 (Album 143)
  - VC 1913 — Jerome, Albertina (Pitkin), undated (Album 145)
  - VC 1913 — Mosenthal, Lucy (Penniman), undated (Album 166)
  - VC 1913 — Nims, Pauline (Pratt), undated (Album 138)
  - VC 1913 — Nims, Pauline (Pratt), undated (Album 139)
  - VC 1913 — Ogden, Neida (Quackenbush), undated (Album 167)
  - VC 1913 — Ordway, Katherine Gretta, undated (Album 151)
  - VC 1913 — Rice, Louisa (Taylor) [with 2 loose pages], circa 1909-1913 (Album 338)
  - VC 1913 — Rivenburg, Narola E., undated (Album 142)
  - VC [1913?] — Unidentified, 1909-1913 (Album 340)
  - VC 1914 — Babbott, Elizabeth (French), undated (Album 216)
  - VC 1914 — Boyden, Alice G., undated (Album 140)
  - VC 1914 — Boyden, Alice G., undated (Album 141)
  - VC 1914 — Dewees, Edith (Hilles), undated (Album 215)
  - VC 1914 — Dewees, Edith (Hilles), undated (Album 219)
  - VC 1914 — Finn, Mona (Cowell), undated (Album 217)
  - VC 1914 — Mosscrop, Alfreda, undated (Album 218)
  - VC 1914 — Pettengill, Dorothy (Blackall), undated (Album 203)
  - VC 1914 — Robbins, Harriet Chase (Album 276)
  - VC 1914 — Robbins, Harriet Chase (Album 277)
  - VC 1914 — Sarris, Helen (Stevens), undated (Album 197)
  - VC 1914 — Scott, Ina, undated (Album 172)
  - VC 1914 — Skinner, Elisabeth, 1913-1914 (Album 295)
  - VC 1914 — Stone, Georgina R., undated (Album 163)
  - VC 1914 — West, Laura S., circa 1914 (Album 342)
  - VC 1914 — Unidentified, circa 1910-1914 (Album 146)
  - VC 1914 — Unidentified, circa 1910-1914 (Album 198)
  - VC 1914 — Unidentified, circa 1910-1914 (Album 214)
  - VC 1914 — Unidentified (Album 220)
  - VC 1914 — Unidentified, circa 1910-1914 (Album 303)
  - VC 1915 — Conway, Charlotte (Eaton), undated (Album 253)
  - VC 1915 — Finn, Mona (Cowell), undated (Album 199)
  - VC 1915 — Gannett, Mary (Ross), undated (Album 240)
  - VC 1915 — Hooker, Helen (Ferris), undated (Album 221)
  - VC 1915 — Moore, Nancy Campbell, circa 1911-1915 (Album 314)
  - VC 1915 — Moore, Nancy Campbell, circa 1907-1919 (Album 315)
  - VC 1915 — Moore, Nancy Campbell, circa 1905-1911 (Album 316)
  - VC 1915 — Sherwin, Martha May (Reynolds), undated (Album 191)
  - VC 1915 — Sherwin, Martha May (Reynolds), undated (Album 192)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A., undated (Album 248)
  - VC 1915 — Truesdell, Julia Newton (Brooks), 1911-1915 (Album 311)
  - VC [1915?] — Unidentified, 1911-1915 (Album 305)
  - VC 1916 — Barnes, Christine White, undated (Album 176)
  - VC 1916 — Barnes, Christine White, undated (Album 177)
  - VC 1916 — Daggett, Louiseanna (Hess) [partial album, gift of Louise Daggett McKiddy (VC 45-4)], circa 1916 (Album 255)
  - VC 1916 — Flickinger, Jean, undated (Album 224)
  - VC 1916 — Mapes, Gladys (Blakeslee), circa 1913-1916 (Album 5)
  - VC 1916 — Markwick, Marjorie (Anthony), circa 1912-1916 (Album 223)
  - VC 1916 — Ralli, Elaine P., circa 1900-1916 (Album 302)
  - VC 1916 — Rannells, Marion E., undated (Album 252)
  - VC 1916 — Tatnall, Helen (Shaw), undated (Album 256)
  - VC Class of 1916 — "Photographs from Senior Picture Sale", undated (Album 341)
  - VC 1917 — Anthony, Constance, circa 1913-1917 (Album 222)
  - VC 1917 — Beebe, Olive (Lapham), undated (Album 242)
  - VC 1917 — Blood-Smyth, Gertrude (Haff), 1913-1916 (Album 296)
  - VC 1917 — Diamond, Elizabeth (Stafford), undated (Album 244)
  - VC 1917 — Greenleaf, Elisabeth (Bristol), 1913-1917, 1937 (Album 317)
  - VC 1917 — Krick, E. Kathryn, 1912-1914 (Album 284.a)
  - VC 1917 — Krick, E. Kathryn, 1916 (Album 284.b)
  - VC 1917 — Owens, Horatia, undated (Album 200)
  - VC 1917 — Thorburn, Helen C., undated (Album 174)
  - VC 1917 — Thorburn, Helen C., undated (Album 175)
  - VC 1917 — Unidentified, circa 1913-1917 (Album 245)
  - VC 1918 — Gans, Mary P., undated (Album 247)
  - VC Ex 1918 — Hamilton, Mary (Gaines), undated (Album 226)
  - VC Ex 1918 — Hunter, Clarence B.K., undated (Album 225)
  - VC 1918 — Jacobs, Rhea (Fisher), undated (Album 272.a)
  - VC 1918 — Jacobs, Rhea (Fisher), undated (Album 272.b)
  - VC 1918 — Morris, Aimee R., undated (Album 238)
  - VC 1918 — Moss, Margaret Morris (Benney), undated (Album 236)
  - VC 1918 — Moss, Margaret Morris (Benney), undated (Album 237)
  - VC 1918 — Stevens, Lois (Carver), undated (Album 243)
  - VC 1918 — Unidentified [housed with Album no. 130], circa 1914-1918 (Album 178)
  - VC 1918 — Wheeler, Gladys (Lawrence), circa 1916-1918 (Album 336)
  - VC [1918?] — Unidentified — loose pages of personal photos, including Edna St. Vincent Millay as Marie de France [housed with Album no. 130], circa 1914-1918 (Album 300)
  - Randolph-Macon Woman's College, Class of 1918 — Snyder, Grace (Rollins) (Album 246)
  - VC 1919 — Dunn, Marjorie, circa 1915-1919 (Album 301)
  - VC Ex 1919 — Fitt, Emma Moody, undated (Album 228)
  - VC 1919 — Momsen, Dorothea (Harnecker), undated (Album 227)
  - VC 1919 — Towle, Florence, 1915-1919 (Album 326)
  - VC 1919 — Unidentified, circa 1919 (Album 287)
  - VC 1919 — Wellington, Anne, undated (Album 230)
  - VC 1920 — Carr, Mary Patience (Album 273)
  - VC 1920 — Unidentified [Eleanor Parsons?], 1915-1920 (Album 190)
  - VC 1920 — Whitehead, Harriet V. (Burpee), circa 1919-1922 (Album 289)
  - VC 1921 — Baxter, Phebe (Poole), undated (Album 241)
  - VC 1921 — MacGregor, Catherine Scott, 1917-1921 (Album 335)
  - VC 1922 — Baker, Mary (Howe) [partial album], undated (Album 254)
  - VC 1922 — Bozyan, Margaret (Bliss), 1918-1922 (Album 196)
  - VC 1922 — Calvin, Ruth (Goodkind) — including images of travel through the American West [see Ruth (Goodkind) Calvin Photograph Album ], 1918-1923
  - VC 1922 — Carroll, Ruth (Robinson), undated (Album 239)
  - VC 1922 — Geddes, Mildred (Purdy), undated (Album 193)
  - VC 1922 — Mills, Louise (Morris) (Album 250)
  - VC 1922 — Morrison, Edith Grace, 1918-1922 (Album 299)
  - VC 1922 — Van Brunt, Catherine S., undated (Album 232)
  - VC 1922 — Weston, Faith (Borton) — personal photos, undated (Album 213)
  - VC 1923 — Richardson, Margaret H. (Laidlaw) [see Margaret H. Laidlaw Richarson Papers ], 1919-1923
  - VC 1924 — Janish, Jeanne (Russell) — Reunion, circa 1974 (Album 271)
  - VC 1924 — Janish, Jeanne (Russell) — Vassar College campus and friends, 1920-1924 (Album 270)
  - VC 1924 — Unidentified, circa 1920-1924 (Album 304)
  - VC 1925 — Brydon, Anne Page [partial album], undated (Album 212)
  - VC Ex 1925 — Sauber, Emily J., circa 1907-1911 (Album 328)
  - VC 1926 — Garnsey, Gertrude, undated (Album 262)
  - VC 1926 — McAllister, Mary (Baldwin), undated (Album 251)
  - VC 1927 — Montgomery, Charlotte "Shady" (Nichols), undated (Album 249)
  - VC 1927 — Reid, Mabel, circa 1923-1927 (Album 310)
  - VC 1929 — Irmisch, Alice (Karslake), undated (Album 231)
  - VC 1930 — [Voorhees, Florence?], circa 1926-1930 (Album 324)
  - VC 1931 — Hobby, Gladys, 1927-1928 (Album 268)
  - VC 1931 — Hobby, Gladys, 1929-1930 (Album 269)
  - VC 1933 — Maclaurin, Elfriede (Carter), undated (Album 257)
  - VC 1936 — Barnes, Mary (Dilworth) — Vassar College buildings [housed with Album no. 130], 1930s (Album 194)
  - VC 1936 — Barnes, Mary (Dilworth) — VC Chapel, 1930s (Album 208)
  - VC 1937 — Jack, Martha Turley, 1933-1939 (Album 313)
  - VC 1939 — Evers, Lucy Frances (Reed)— Vassar scenes and classmates as well as Evers'cousin (once removed) Winifred Smith, 1938-1941 (Album 308)
  - VC 1940 — Harrison, Nancy (Blaine) (Album 337)
  - VC 1948 — Crocker, Julie Schoepf, circa 1946 (Album 330)
  - VC 1948 — Midas Meyers, Margaret, circa 1944-1948 (Album 321)
  - Margaret De M. Brown (photographer) - VC Wimpfheimer Nursery School [formerly Album no. 260, see Margaret De M. Brown Photographs], 1920s-1940s
  - Margaret De M. Brown (photographer) - VC buildings, grounds, and events [formerly Album no. 278, see Margaret De M. Brown Photographs], 1920s
  - Miscellany News Staff — Vassar plays [formerly Album no. 259, see Philalethan Society Records], circa 1980-1989
  - Vail Brothers (photographers) [formerly Album no. 266, see Vail Brothers Photograph Albums ]
  - Warren Kay Vantine (photographer) [formerly Album no. 267, see Warren Kay Vantine Photographs]
  - Unidentified, 1871-1877 (Album 30)
  - Unidentified, 1872-1875 (Album 45)
  - Unidentified, 1880s (Album 182)
  - Unidentified, circa 1897-1901 (Album 279)
  - Unidentified — VC Views, 1900 (Album 188)
  - Unidentified [partial album], 1901 (Album 121)
  - Unidentified [partial album], 1901 (Album 122)
  - Unidentified, 1905-1908 (Album 202)
  - Unidentified, 1905-1909 (Album 209)
  - Unidentified, circa 1909-1911 (Album 168)
  - Unidentified, circa 1909-1917 (Album 333)
  - Unidentified, circa 1910 (Album 297)
  - Unidentified, 1911-1915 (Album 180)
  - Unidentified, circa 1911-1913 (Album 334)
  - Unidentified, circa 1911-1918 (Album 332)
  - Unidentified, 1912-1915 (Album 184)
  - Unidentified, [1914?] (Album 173)
  - Unidentified — VC 50th Anniversary, 1915 (Album 207)
  - Unidentified, 1916-1918 (Album 159)
  - Unidentified — Summer Institute of Euthenics, 1929-1936 (Album 263)
  - Unidentified, 1944-1945 (Album 195)
  - Unidentified, [before 1946] (Album 211)
- Series XII. Artwork and Projects, 2025
  - VC 2025 — Straw, Sydney — Experiential Map of Vassar College, [ink on paper] (Map Case - Drawer 33)